what's up visionaries today i'm doing a
quick open box on my new
stand-up hairdryer i purchased from my
favorite online store amazon
to achieve this gorgeous deep
conditioned
twist out it is so bomb y'all
if you want to purchase this as well i
will have a link in the description
below
let's get started so the unboxing was
really easy not a lot of pieces
to the hairdryer so i really like that
about this product
building it was going to be super fast i
hate those
foam pieces they get all over the house
so i was trying to do my best to keep
them in the box
the instructions were a little confusing
towards the end
you have to read them a couple times to
kind of get what it's saying
it's not very detailed and i felt like
it was missing one piece that you needed
to build this properly and a lot of
people
didn't know so that's why they got some
not so okay reviews on amazon
but i eventually figured it out and i'll
explain that
in this video but instructions could
have been way better
to be honest
[Music]
so
so this is the part where it gets tricky
for a lot of people
you cannot put the tube in the hole
because that silver piece at the bottom
is still on it
so i made this mistake and i was trying
to figure it out because the
instructions
did not tell you exactly how to do it if
you don't take the screw and the silver
piece off the wheels will not be steady
and they will keep falling off so first
you want to put this black
piece as circular in the middle on the
wheels
it connects all the wheels together hold
the wheels in place
and then you want to take that silver
piece and screw
off the pole this is the piece you have
to take off the bottom of the pole
this is the part they don't tell you you
need something like this to be able to
unscrew the screw that's at the bottom
of the pole
now i can easily push the hole into the
feet connection
and i can screw this screw
underneath the feet and the feet
connection so that
everything stays in place the feet as
well as the hair dryer
and make sure it's the hair dry it does
not tip over and everything is secure
i love that you can adjust the height
you can have it
high or you can have it really low for
maybe a child or if you want to sit on a
stupor pillows
so this is the enclosure door where your
head will go
and this is a timer
it goes from zero to 60 minutes you have
the on and off switch
and then you have your temperature it
can go from cool to very high up to 75
degrees
you must start the timer and press the
on button in order for it to work
it makes a very low sound if you can
hear it which is really nice for a hair
[Applause]
dryer
i'm going to deep condition my hair and
see how it goes
i don't get a hood proof that you can
make it through the glue
celebrations on the roof dang i waited
and waited patiently waiting lost my
time for real
i'm great in the making stuff that i'm
taking make sure i'm getting it in
[\h__\h] what you thought about the boss
look how connected we is
looking around the view getting better
see we taking off for real
see that's why i flash forever with
flexing nothing you can tell me
[Music]
the mouth i'm in this head from the
mouth
i mean this hit from the mouth
i'm from the home of the brain [\h__\h]
told me never touching
[Music]
all of my family died i hope they rest
in peace i pray to god for peace but
[\h__\h] be playing for keep so i keep
that
on me to sleep i got a family
and i got once
[Music]
looking around of you getting better see
we taking off for real
see that's why i flash forever with flex
ain't nothing
the dryer did a really great job at
drying my hair
really fast and efficient the deep
conditioner penetrated
all my strands my hair is so moist
and defined and just nice so i give this
product two thumbs up i recommend it
if you would like to purchase it as well
it's a link in the description where you
can purchase
i been wanting to stand up hair dryer
for a while
so i'm glad i finally was able to get it
at a great price
[Music]
to my channel guys like my video please
share comment let me know what you think
what you may want me
to do a product review on next time
and have a great day i think i got it i
know that i got it see i'm in my bag for
real the rapper they trying you know how
they trying but they just can't pass the
kid
you [\h__\h] get chances so many chances
now i'm just getting it in
i cry from the back and now i'm in
france you gotta need my parts for real
oh what you thought the [\h__\h] was done
see your woman nothing to say
i'm at your door to your neck trying to
make it lose your breath
celebration for the wealth i don't do
this for my health
by myself nobody else wifey told me give
them hell
but i told them wishing well wishing
from a wishing well
more ends less airs more life less
shells look
real love or fake get that out my face